<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Trevor F. Freeman</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Trevor F. Freeman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Python post for the project</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/09/python-post-for-the-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/09/python-post-for-the-project/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I’ve run Python code in a Jupyter notebook many times, but I wasn’t aware that it could be run within an Rmarkdown file. Not only is it possible to knit Python code in an Rmarkdown file, but you can actually make R and Python play together. I’m going to show off just a little bit of that here but keep it pretty simple.
 Running python code in an Rmarkdown file Then, to run Python code it’s as simple as making a python code chunk (using {python}) and run your code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nonsense post</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/08/nonsense-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/08/nonsense-post/</guid>
      <description>It seems like someone in my apartment constantly has a car alarm going off, and they have the hardest time getting it turned off. This just happened pretty late at night, and I was afraid my dog was going to start barking at the sudden noise. Thankfully she stayed quiet, but she was definitely annoyed. I feel you girl - if I could make it stop I definitely would.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
